在本节课 我们将介绍如何...
For this lession, We're going to cover how to...
在官网下载并安装启动器
go to the CRYENGINE portal, download the launcher, install the launcher.
并设置好启动器
And then get up and running at least with the launcher
以准备好在下一个视频中 安装引擎并创建项目
to proceed with the next video in which you will install the engine and create a project.
如你所见 我已经登上了官网
So as we can see, on our screen, I have the CRYENGINE site,
也就是登陆cryengine.com
so if I go to cryengine.com.
在此视频中 你现在看到的是The Climb页面
You're presented with The Climb as this is one of our current videos,
你可选择"PAY WHAT YOU WHAT" 点下它
and you can choose to Pay What You What in this click
或者选择"GO TO CRYENGINE.COM"
or let's go to the "GO TO CRYENGINE.COM".
我们一进入官网
So once we go to cryengine.com,
我们可以看见一个全新页面
we can see that we have a whole new portal
上面都有 市场 学习 社区 之类的东西
with marketplace and learning, some community stuff,
重要的是我们要获取CRYENGINE
but more importantly, we want to get CRYENGINE.
而要想获取CRYENGINE
In order to get CRYENGINE,
我们得先登陆账户
we have to have a login.
所以我们点击"GET CRYENGINE"
So let's click on "GET CRYENGINE"
然后它就会跳转到 PWYW页面
and this brings us to the Pay What You Want model
这个PWYW也是CE的新商业模式
which is the new business model that we're using at Crytek.
你可以选择"€0" 然后点"GET STARTED NOW"
So let's click on "GET STARTED NOW", you can go ahead and select 0
这样 DEV FUND 和 CRYTEK 都是€0
on the DEV FUND, 0 to CRYTEK,
因为这个教程中 我们不打算花钱
because we're not giving any money in this case.
点了"GET STARTED NOW"之后 它让我们输入邮箱 账户名和密码
So if we get started now, we can see that we're supposed to have an email, user name and password.
但这些我们都没有 所以我们得注册个账户
We don't have either of those, so we need to register.
所以我点"Register now"
So if I click on "Register now",
然后输入账户名
I'm going to choose the "ceText1984" (1984) for my date of birth,
然后输入你的邮箱
and then I'm going to do "cetest1984@gmail.com"
这个邮箱还是我特意为这个视频注册的
which I have set up specifically for this video.
然后输入账户密码
I'm going to type in my password.
最后输入上面的验证码
And then, finally, I'm going type in the number as seen above.
So 4746.
4  7  4  6
然后"Create Account"
Create my account.
接下来进入账户细节
Now we're going to go to some account details
考虑到你以后可能要订阅东西
considering that you may want to do some subscription.
我们收集一些关于你住在哪的信息
We take a little bit more information regarding where you're at.
所以我这里填Crytek
So let's go ahead and do Crytek,
我在这里输入111 Avenue
I'm going to type in 111 Avenue.
然后我这里输入111
And then we can do 111.
这里我就输入我的邮编
And then I'll just do my own postal code from
US的邮编
United States.
我这里也选择美国
We're going to choose United States.
我在这里输入姓名
I'm going to type in my first and last name.
然后我点同意License Agreement
And I'm going to agree to the License Agreement.
（这里输错了 删掉）
I'm going to delete that cause it's not right.
然后我们选"Save and continue"
And we'll save it and continue.
这里我们让浏览器保存下密码
Press "Save".
然后这里显示 “感谢你使用CE 欢迎来到我们的开发社区
So it says "Thank you for for using CRYENGINE, and welcome to our community,
我们很高兴你的加入”
we're glad to have you."
所以现在 我们应该能下载启动器了
So now we're able to download the launcher.
只需要点击"DOWNLOAD LAUNCHER"
So I'm gonna click "DOWNLOAD THE LAUNCHER",
我这下载的还挺快的
and I'm download relatively quickly.
现在我可以继续下一步 打开安装包
And now I can go ahead and execute the launcher.
所以我这一步点"Install"
So I'm going to install.
这一步是让你选择安装路径
And this is where I'm going to place it.
实际上 我要让它安装到C盘根目录
Actually, let's go ahead and place it directly on the C drive.
然后我们就进入了安装阶段
And then we'll go through the install process.
还有一件我要做的事是进入邮箱
And one thing I need to make sure is I need to come back to my Gmail
也就是我注册时的邮箱 ctest1984
which is ctest1984.
这里有封邮件说我得激活CE账户
And it's going to say that I need to activate my account.
趁它还在安装时 我先激活一下 不然没法登陆
I'm doing this while it's installing, because if I don't do it, we won't be able to login.
那我这里点"ACTIVATE ACCOUNT"
So I'm gonna activate the account.
我们又到了登陆页面 我点"LOGIN"的话
And now we've come back and if I login,
它右上角就显示你登陆了 ceText1984
I can see that I have ceTest1984.
现在我们就等它安装完
And now we'll wait for the installer to finish.
说完 它就装完了
Which it has.
然后我们点"Finish"
And we click "finish".
默认来说它会自动打开启动器
By default, it'll start up and your launcher will be on the screen.
我们先回来一下 看下我的用户名
And let's go back in here, and check out my name.
我的用户名是 ceText1984
So this is ceText1984
然后输入我的密码
We're type in my password.
这里我勾选"Remember me" 记住我
I'm going to say yes I want it to remember me.
然后登陆
I'm going to login.
现在我已经登陆到启动器
And now I've logged in to my launcher.
一切都正常
Everything works.
现在我已经准备好进入下一个视频
And I'm prepared to continue on to the next video after this
下一期将介绍如何下载引擎
on how to download the engine itself
如何创建一个项目 并查看它的目录
and then create a new project and expose it inside of our folder
并最终启动引擎
to eventually launch the engine.
翻译：他出院了